I have made over 500 pints in the Ninja
Creamy, and this is my favorite recipe
I've ever made. Welcome back to my
series where I recreate Dairy Queen
Blizzard flavors, but lower in calories
and higher in protein. This is the Royal
New York Cheesecake Blizzard. Let me
show you how to make it. So, you just
saw me make my classic vanilla base. The
full recipe for that will be down in the
description. While that is freezing, you
can grab some strawberries. I use frozen
strawberries. You can also use fresh,
toss them up with some sweetener, and
then throw them in the fridge to merate.
That will be part one of our mix-ins.
And now part two are these cheesecake
bites. So, I just bought this little
cheesecake from the store, chopped it up
into little bite-sized pieces, and then
coated it in some graham cracker dust.
I'm sure you could also find some
pre-made cheesecake bites that are
pretty similar. Now, back to the ice
cream. The key to this recipe is
actually the fact that we didn't fill
our pint up to the fill line. When you
do this, the creamy can't blend it
completely. So, it basically puts all
the ice cream out to the side and
creates a hole in the middle of the
pint. So, while that might seem like a
flaw, it actually creates the perfect
opportunity to make these Dairy Queen
loaded blizzards. So, you can just load
in your strawberry topping, cheesecake
bites, and the rest of your graham
cracker dust. And then you have one of
the greatest creations I have ever made.
So, if you've never tried one of my
recipes, let this be the first